Isabel Mill

Full Stack Developer

Full Stack Developer with knowledge and experience in writing single-page applications using the latest WEB technologies such as Node.js, Vue.js, Vuex, React.js, and Angular.

Well-organized person, problem solver with high attention to detail that constantly explores new ideas and technologies.

Latest project: Trello clone (VUE3, Node.js, MongoDB):

https://tasko-proj.herokuapp.com

Portfolio: https://isabel-mill.herokuapp.com/

Experience

Technical Operation Specialist - Gett, Tel Aviv

Jul 2020 - Dec 2021

- Connected drivers to Gett application.
- Developed spreadsheets and databases to track and measure sales activities.
- Analyzed and reported on performance and sales data.
- Created detailed monthly promotions and employee bonus reports.
- Assisted in developing automated processes to increase teamwork efficiency.

Real Estate Agent - Home Place, Tel Aviv

Jul 2020 - Dec 2021

- Managed contracts, negotiations, and all aspects of sales to finalize purchases and exceed customer expectations.
- Advertised client properties through websites, social media, and real estate guides.
- Sold a high volume of properties in short timeframes to exceed quotas and maximize business revenue.

Intelligence Units Recruiter - IDF, Ramat Gan

Jul 2020 - Dec 2021

- Managed guidance of candidates designating for intelligence units service and recording the process by using CRM software.
- Planned and launched large-scale interviews and tryouts.
- Summarized results and provided the best candidates possible following every unit's unique requirements.

Education

Coding Academy — Full-stack Bootcamp

Jan 2022 - May 2022

Alliance High School — High School Diploma

2013 - 2016

E-mail isabelmavd2@gmail.com

Address Tel Aviv, Israel

Phone 054-4272437

Social Links
<Linkedin> <Github>

Tech-Skills

HTML
CSS / Sass
Javascript
React
VUE
Angular
Node.js
MongoDB
Git
Microsoft Office

Languages

English - fluent Hebrew - native Russian - mother tongue French - basic